brightnetwork.co.uk 2016-02-16

# Privacy Policy | Bright Network

We at Bright Network value your membership and understand just how important it is to protect your data. Please take the time to review the Privacy Policy carefully in conjunction with the Terms of Use, as by using www.brightnetwork.co.uk (the "Website"), you agree to be unconditionally bound by this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use.

#### What information will we use?

By becoming a member of the Bright Network, we will collect and use information about you. This information includes but is not limited to your registration details, education and career information and your relevant activity on the Bright Network (together "your information").

#### Who will we share your information with?

On becoming a Network Member and expressly agreeing to the Terms of Use, you consent for us to share your information within Bright Network.  

We will only share your information with companies registered as partners and clients of Bright Network, as well as selected third parties deemed appropriate by Bright Network once we have gained prior consent from you. 

For example, if you have applied for a Bright Network event and submitted your CV as part of that application, we will share that CV with the client firm who is hosting and/or attending the event. This will only be done so in accordance with the terms and conditions of that particular event of which you will be notified of at the time of applying. 

Other than the disclosures referred to in this policy, we will not disclose any personal information without your permission unless we are legally entitled or obliged to do so.

#### How will your information be used?

We may analyse and use your information to see what kind of career interests you have and make suggestions that we think will interest you. We will also use your information to select and send information on opportunities, products or services which are likely to interest you.

#### What choices do I have?

You can choose any of the following options about the information you receive from Bright Network:

  1. Choose to receive marketing information from Bright Network about jobs; events; advice and Bright Networks clients and third parties deemed appropriate by Bright Network. This is the default option that becomes active when you accept our Terms and Conditions and Privacy Policy;
  2. You can choose to select all or none of these 4 options.

In order to exercise your choices as listed above, simply vist the profile section on your account and customise them accordingly.

#### Transferring your information outside the European Economic Area

Network member data is stored with Salesforce.com a provider which stores data outside of the European Economic Area, mainly in the US. These countries may not have similar data protection laws to the EEA. We will endeavour to ensure that your privacy rights continue to be protected.

#### IP addresses

When you visit the Website, we log your IP address (the unique address which identifies your computer on the internet) which is automatically recognised by our web server. We do not link IP addresses to personally identifiable information.

If a Network Member thinks an unauthorised person has become aware of any Bright Network password, they should contact Bright Network immediately. We cannot be responsible for any unauthorised use of a Network Member's profile or unauthorised activity on the Website.

#### Transfer of ownership

If we sell or transfer Bright Network to another company we may transfer all of our rights and obligations under these terms of use without any further consent and may disclose or transfer all information we hold about Network Members or prospective Network Members to a prospective or actual new owner. Such a disclosure or transfer will not alter the rights of such Network Members in respect of the use that can be made of such information by such other company.

#### Right to request information

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you. If you would like a copy of the information held on you, please write to: Bright Network, 5th Floor, Goldsmiths House, 137 - 141 Regent Street London W1B 4HZ.

#### Security

We have implemented technology and policies to safeguard your privacy from unauthorised access and improper use and will continue to review these measures from time to time.

#### Third party sites

Bright Network takes no responsibility for the privacy policies of any third party sites even if access is linked via the Bright Network. We would recommend that you check the policy of each external site you visit.

#### How do I check or change my data choices?

In the first instance, should you wish to check or change your data choices, you should log into your Bright Network account and navigate to your profile to edit accprdingly.

Should you have any problems in doing this, you can contact us either by logging onto the Website, emailing us at hello@brightnetwork.co.uk, calling the Bright Network offices or writing to us at our registered office address.

Bright Network (UK) Limited is registered with the ICO as entry Z1258381.
